Amadeus Folego Curriculum vitae

## AMADEUS FOLEGO DA SILVA

Born in Mauá, SP, 23/12/1988 - Single 220, Carlos Turner st., ap. 1302, Belo Horizonte - MG, 31140-520

CONTACT INFO Email: amadeusfolego@gmail.com Phone: 55 11 94807-0450

Github: @badosu

PROFILE Versatile professional, with experience developing for the web using many technologies.

Interested in Math, Computer Science, Audio Processing and *Hacking* in general. Has familiarity, and good learning skills, for concepts and technologies which are

relevant for the web.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

03/2017 Toptal https://toptal.com

Consultant

10/2014 Presumé http://presume.com.br

Technical partner at Presumé: a platform for pre-interviewing candidates.

**08/2015 - 03/2016 Pegcar** http://pegcar.com

Peer-to-peer car sharing service. Cofounder

12/2013 - 10/2014 Stackbuilders http://stackbuilders.com

Web development consultancy company based on NY. Many different projects.

05/2013 - 10/2013 Palpiteros http://palpiteros.com

A football social platform, built with Backbone, RoR and some other tools.

11/2012 - 04/2013 ClickARQ http://clickarq.com.br

Architecture crowdsourcing startup, where I worked as CTO and the only developer.

**06/2012 - 12/2012 Codeminer42** http://codeminer42.com

Worked in several startup projects, with Ruby, Java and Python.

06/2010 - 05/2012 Boo-box, Betboo

Previous workplaces, started doing web-development with .Net and Ruby.

## **PROJECTS**

- Statesman Sequel https://github.com/badosu/statesman-sequel Statesman adapter for Sequel
- Sidekiq https://github.com/mperham/sidekiq/pull/3075

  Migrated the existing web monitor from Sinatra to pure Rack
- Sine Synth https://github.com/badosu/sine\_synth.lv2
  A sine waveform synthesizer

ACADEMIC QUALIFICATIONS

**01/2010** (unfinished) **B.Sc. Mathematics** Universidade Federal do ABC **2006 B.Sc. Science and Technology** Universidade Federal do ABC

Dynamic modelling of the Magnetic Hysteresis phenomenon
 Available at (pt-br): http://www.scribd.com/doc/21709933